supershareware.com 2011-12-31

# Super Shareware: Privacy Statement

**Privacy Statement**

Super Shareware is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Super Shareware Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Super Shareware website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.  

**Collection of your Personal Information**  
There is information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Super Shareware. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Super Shareware for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Super Shareware Web site.

Super Shareware keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Super Shareware, in order to determine what Super Shareware services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Super Shareware to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. Super Shareware uses web log analysis software on its server and keep the reports for internal use; Super Shareware does not use these reports to identify individual users except in cases of deliberate mis-use of our systems.

The World Birthday Web does not disclose email addresses; they are kept confidential, and greetings can only be sent via a web form which includes extensive protections against automated submission. We never sell e-mail addresses to third parties (for instance, to bulk e-mail advertisers). 

Super Shareware does not sell nor make available to the public postal mail addresses, phone numbers, or other information gathered during business transactions or software submissions with our customers, software authors. Super Shareware Web sites will disclose any personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Super Shareware or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Super Shareware; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Super Shareware, or the public.

**Use of Cookies**  
The Super Shareware Web site use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Super Shareware pages, or register with any Super Shareware services, a cookie helps supershareware.com to recall your specific information on subsequent visits.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Super Shareware services or Web sites you visit.

**Ad Servers Privacy**  
We have contracted with Kontera and Google AdSense to monitor certain pages of our website for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisement 'click-throughs', and/or other activities on our website. Where authorized by us, Kontera and Google AdSense may use cookies, web beacons, and/or other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about our website visitors. No personally identifiable information is collected by or transferred to any party other than the Advertiser. 

S **ecurity of your Personal Information**  
Super Shareware secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Super Shareware secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

**  
External Links**  
Super Shareware provides external links to other websites, mainly software developers websites . Super Shareware is not responsible and cannot control the content and security of other sites you visit once you leave Super Shareware website.  Software programs made available at Super Shareware website are hosted  from servers all over the world. Super Shareware does not host any software in its server. Super Shareware makes no representations as to the content of externally hosted  software files or that the files and programs are accurate, complete, virus-free or do not infringe the rights of any third party. When downloading, each user is responsible to virus check any program from the Super Shareware site before installation. Super Shareware is not responsible for any loss or damage resulting from users downloading or use of any such programs or files.

**Contact Information**  
Super Shareware welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Super Shareware has not adhered to this Statement, please [contact us](mailto:info8@supershareware.com) , We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
